<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2019-2020 Wouter Wijsman <wwijsman@live.nl> -->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>io.github.sharkwouter.Minigalaxy</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>Minigalaxy</name>
  <summary>A simple GOG client for Linux</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
        Minigalaxy lets you download, install and play your GOG Linux games without getting in your way.
        </p>
    <p> Besides all that, it offers the following additional features:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Select in which language you'd prefer to download your games</li>
      <li>Change where games are installed</li>
      <li>Search your GOG Linux library</li>
      <li>Show all games or just the ones you've installed</li>
      <li>View the error message if a game fails to launch</li>
      <li>Enable displaying the FPS in games</li>
    </ul>
    <p>An account on gog.com is required to use this application.</p>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">io.github.sharkwouter.Minigalaxy.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Minigalaxy</caption>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/sharkwouter/minigalaxy/master/screenshot.jpg</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/sharkwouter/minigalaxy</url>
  <developer_name>Wouter "sharkwouter" Wijsman</developer_name>
  <provides>
    <binary>minigalaxy</binary>
  </provides>
  <releases><release version="1.3.1" date="2024-11-26">
      <description>
        <p>Implements the following changes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix Windows games with multiple parts not installing with wine</li>
          <li>Minor AppData fixes (thanks to tim77)</li>
          <li>Added Portuguese translation (thanks to GLSWV)</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release><release version="1.3.0" date="2024-06-10">
      <description>
        <p>Implements the following changes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix Remove forward slash from desktop filename for Shenzhen I/O (thanks to slowsage)</li>
          <li>Fix race when preparing download location (thanks to viacheslavka)</li>
          <li>Fix multithreaded downloads of Windows games (thanks to viacheslavka)</li>
          <li>Fix DLC installation for Windows games (thanks to viacheslavka)</li>
          <li>Allow users to specify the download directory (thanks to viacheslavka)</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release><release version="1.2.6" date="2024-01-19">
      <description>
        <p>Implements the following changes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix changing the install path causing an exception</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release><release version="1.2.5" date="2023-08-11">
      <description>
        <p>Implements the following changes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix filtering for installed games</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release><release version="1.2.4" date="2023-08-11">
      <description>
        <p>Implements the following changes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix packages missing a script</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release><release version="1.2.3" date="2023-08-11">
      <description>
        <p>Implements the following changes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix short freeze on startup (thanks to LeXofLeviafan)</li>
          <li>Fix game information not showing in list view (thanks to TotalCaesar659)</li>
          <li>Hide A Plague Tale Digital Goodies Pack (thanks to TotalCaesar659)</li>
          <li>Remove round corners from top of the "play" button (thanks to lmeunier)</li>
          <li>Move the Gametile menu button alongside the Play button (thanks to lmeunier)</li>
          <li>Update Spanish translation (thanks to manurtinez)</li>
          <li>Capitalize first letter of the "play/download/..." button (thanks to lmeunier)</li>
          <li>Update Traditional Chinese translation (thanks to s8321414)</li>
          <li>Added additional tooltips to buttons, labels, menu items and radio buttons (thanks to orende)</li>
          <li>Hide CDPR Goodie Pack Content</li>
          <li>Add notifications on successful download and installation of games (thanks to orende)</li>
          <li>Add category filtering dialog for game library (thanks to orende)</li>
          <li>Parallelize api.can_connect function with threads, futures (thanks to orende)</li>
          <li>Fix available disk space being checked in parent directory (thanks to Unrud)</li>
          <li>Create new config if reading it fails</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release><release version="1.2.2" date="2022-09-27">
      <description>
        <p>Implements the following changes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix progress bar not showing up for downloads</li>
          <li>Fix downloads not being cancellable</li>
          <li>Fix incompatibility with python 3.6</li>
          <li>Fix connection error texts (thanks to TotalCaesar659)</li>
          <li>Show DLC titles in English (thanks to TotalCaesar659)</li>
          <li>Fix version not being updated during a release</li>
          <li>Update Norwegian Bokmål translation (thanks to kimmalmo)</li>
          <li>Update Czech translation (thanks to jakbuz23)</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release><release version="1.2.1" date="2022-09-19">
      <description>
        <p>Implements the following changes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix downloads failing when content length is not returned by the server</li>
          <li>Allow different types of downloads to happen at the same time (thanks to jgerrish)</li>
          <li>Fix metadata file having releases in wrong order</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release><release version="1.2.0" date="2022-09-19">
      <description>
        <p>Implements the following changes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Split game information and properties into different windows (thanks to TotalCaesar659)</li>
          <li>Add list view (thanks to TotalCaesar659)</li>
          <li>Allow DLC to be queued up for downloading (thanks to flagrama)</li>
          <li>Fix changing library to a directory with special characters in the name (thanks to makson96)</li>
          <li>Fix signing in with Facebook (thanks to phlash)</li>
          <li>Always use cached DLC icons and thumbnails (thanks to TotalCaesar659)</li>
          <li>Cache information covers (thanks to TotalCaesar659)</li>
          <li>Fix installers not being cleaned up like expected (thanks to Kzimir)</li>
          <li>Fix error when opening game properties window when wine is not installed (thanks to lmeunier)</li>
          <li>Fix freeze for games generating a lot of output (thanks to lmeunier)</li>
          <li>Fix extracting rar based games with innoextract (thanks to Kzimir)</li>
          <li>Allow setting wine executable per game (thanks to Kzimir)</li>
          <li>Add GameMode support (thanks to TotalCaesar659)</li>
          <li>Add MangoHud support (thanks to TotalCaesar659)</li>
          <li>Add option to use Winetricks (thanks to TotalCaesar659)</li>
          <li>Fix updates not always being detected directly after opening Minigalaxy (thanks to TotalCaesar659)</li>
          <li>Fix desktop files generated not always being able to launch (thanks to otaconix)</li>
          <li>Show percentage when hovering over download progress bar (thanks to TotalCaesar659)</li>
          <li>Add option to disable update check per game (thanks to TotalCaesar659)</li>
          <li>Add forum, GOG Database and PCGamingWiki URLs to game information (thanks to TotalCaesar659)</li>
          <li>List genre as unknown in game information when none is found (thanks to mareksapota)</li>
          <li>Fix changing installation path causing crashes in rare cases (thanks to makson96)</li>
          <li>Fall back to English when locale cannot be determined (thanks to flagrama)</li>
          <li>Add gettext to build dependencies (thanks to larslindq)</li>
          <li>Improve error handling upon API errors</li>
          <li>Fix several issues with launching Windows games from Minigalaxy</li>
          <li>Fix some games getting stuck on in queue</li>
          <li>Fix Windows game installation not caring about preferred language (thanks to Kzimir)</li>
          <li>Add Greek translation (thanks to Pyrofanis)</li>
          <li>Add Spanish (Spain) translation (thanks to mbarrio)</li>
          <li>Add Romanian (Romania) translation (thanks to xSlendiX)</li>
          <li>Update Norwegian Bokmål translation (thanks to kimmalmo)</li>
          <li>Update Czech translation (thanks to jakbuz23)</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release><release version="1.1.0" date="2021-11-09">
      <description>
        <p>Implements the following changes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Improve integrity check after downloading (thanks to makson96)</li>
          <li>Show an error showing Windows games cannot be enabled</li>
          <li>Add properties menu for games where game specific actions can be made like setting launch options and opening the store page (thanks to Odelpasso and makson96)</li>
          <li>Add a disk space check before downloading (thanks to SvdB-nonp and makson96)</li>
          <li>Use a different color for the play button for installed games</li>
          <li>Put installed games at the top of the list</li>
          <li>Store saved installers in ``~/GOG Games/installer`` by default again (thanks to makson96)</li>
          <li>Remember if the user had the installed filter enabled (thanks to makson96)</li>
          <li>Extract Windows games in the background if Innoextract is available (thanks to makson96)</li>
          <li>Extract Windows games in the background (thanks to Odelpasso)</li>
          <li>Fix installing DLC for Windows games (thanks to makson96)</li>
          <li>Fix an error showing if the user has no games (thanks to makson96)</li>
          <li>Add option to hide games (thanks to TotalCaesar659)</li>
          <li>Ask user if they are sure when logging out (thanks to TotalCaesar659)</li>
          <li>Add a dark theme (thanks to TotalCaesar659)</li>
          <li>Run post install script after installation. This fixes Full Throttle Remastered (thanks to makson96)</li>
          <li>Fix games being shown twice</li>
          <li>Fix crash when GOG is down (thanks to lmeunier)</li>
          <li>Make the language configurable (thanks to TotalCaesar659 and zweif)</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release><release version="1.0.2" date="2021-01-14">
      <description>
        <p>Implements the following changes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix updates sometimes not working</li>
          <li>Fix some games always showing an update is available</li>
          <li>Fix DLC not downloading (thanks to stephanlachnit)</li>
          <li>Fix DLC update option not showing up (thanks to makson96)</li>
          <li>Fix show store page button not showing anymore (thanks to makson96)</li>
          <li>Fix missing thumbnails not being downloaded for already installed games (thanks to makson96)</li>
          <li>Fix the login screen crashing in some cases (thanks to makson96)</li>
          <li>Use the system's icon theme for icons used (thanks to stephanlachnit and makson96)</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release><release version="1.0.1" date="2021-01-07">
      <description>
        <p>Implements the following changes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Open maximized if the window was maximized when last closed (thanks to TotalCaesar659)</li>
          <li>Kept installers are now stored in ~/.cache/minigalaxy/download</li>
          <li>Fix about window displaying wrong version number</li>
          <li>Fix show store page button not showing anymore (thanks to makson96)</li>
          <li>Fix the download manager crashing when an installer has been damaged during downloading (thanks to makson96)</li>
          <li>Fix games showing an update is available while the latest version is installed (thanks to makson96)</li>
          <li>Fix loading the library taking a long time when many games are installed (thanks to makson96)</li>
          <li>Fix Gex not launching</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Added the following translations:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Swedish (thanks to Newbytee)</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Updated the following translations:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Polish (thanks to ArturWroblewski)</li>
          <li>Russian (thanks to TotalCaesar659)</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release><release version="1.0.0" date="2020-11-29">
      <description>
        <p>Implements the following changes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Games can now be updated (thanks to mdgomes and makson96)</li>
          <li>DLC can now be installed and updated (thanks to makson96)</li>
          <li>The installed filter now also shows games which are downloading (thanks to makson96)</li>
          <li>Fix crash on some systems where /usr/bin is linked to /bin (thanks to sgn)</li>
          <li>Create new config file if old one is unreadable (thanks to SvdB-nonp)</li>
          <li>Fix some Windows games not installing because of the directory name used (thanks to SvdB-nonp)</li>
          <li>Fix some Windows games like Witcher 3 not launching because of the working directory not being set (thanks for kibun1)</li>
          <li>Clean up installation files for cancelled downloads (thanks to SvdB-nonp)</li>
          <li>Fix crash on flaky internet connection (thanks to makson96)</li>
          <li>Use 755 permissions for all directories created by Minigalaxy</li>
          <li>Remove cached files when cancelling a download (thanks to svdB-nonp)</li>
          <li>Installed games should no longer be shown twice (thanks to makson96)</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Added the following translations:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Simplified Chinese (thanks to dummyx)</li>
          <li>Spanish (thanks to juanborda)</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Updated the following translations:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Brazilian Portuguese (thanks to EsdrasTarsis)</li>
          <li>Dutch</li>
          <li>French (thanks to Thomasb22)</li>
          <li>German (thanks to BlindJerobine)</li>
          <li>Norwegian Bokmål (thanks to kimmalmo)</li>
          <li>Russian (thanks to protheory8)</li>
          <li>Taiwanese Mandarin (thanks to s8321414)</li>
          <li>Turkish (thanks to fuzunspm</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release><release version="0.9.4" date="2020-04-20">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Added Norwegian Nynorsk translation (thanks to LordPilum).</li>
          <li>Added Russian translation (thanks to protheory8).</li>
          <li>Updated Brazilian Portuguese translation (thanks to EsdrasTarsis).</li>
          <li>Updated French translation (thanks to thomasb22).</li>
          <li>Updated German translation (thanks to BlindJerobine).</li>
          <li>Updated Norwegian Bokmål translation (thanks to kimmalmo).</li>
          <li>Updated Polish translation (thanks to ArturWroblewski).</li>
          <li>Updated Taiwanese Mandarin translation (thanks to s8321414).</li>
          <li>Updated Turkish translation (thanks to fuzunspm).</li>
          <li>Added support for installing Windows games (with help from Odelpasso).</li>
          <li>Added store page link to game menus (thanks to larslindq).</li>
          <li>Fixed game directories being created without any spaces in the name (thanks to larslindq).</li>
          <li>Fixed thumbnails not being downloaded for already installed games.</li>
          <li>Fixed symlinks to libraries not being created correctly upon installation.</li>
          <li>Made preparations for a Flathub package.</li>
          <li>Added all contributors and translators to the about window.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release><release version="0.9.3" date="2020-03-10">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Added German translation (thanks to BlindJerobine).</li>
          <li>Added Turkish translation (thanks to fuzunspm).</li>
          <li>Added Brazilian Portuguese translation (thanks to EsdrasTarsis).</li>
          <li>Added Norwegian Bokmål translation (thanks to kimmalmo).</li>
          <li>Added Polish translation (thanks to ArturWroblewski).</li>
          <li>Added French translation (thanks to thomasb22).</li>
          <li>Added option to cancel downloads.</li>
          <li>Changed the way games are downloaded to a queue instead of trying to download everything at once.</li>
          <li>Added support option to game specific menus which open the GOG support page (thanks to BlindJerobine).</li>
          <li>Ask for confirmation before uninstalling (thanks to Odelpasso).</li>
          <li>Added option to display FPS in games (thanks to Odelpasso).</li>
          <li>Downloads can now be resumed after having been cancelled before.</li>
          <li>Installers are now verified before installing.</li>
          <li>The active download is now resumed when restarting Minigalaxy.</li>
          <li>Fixed issue with games not downloading.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release><release version="0.9.2" date="2020-01-07">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Added a button which allows you to uninstall game.</li>
          <li>Added a button which allows you to open directory in which game is installed.</li>
          <li>Added Dutch translation.</li>
          <li>Added Taiwanese Mandarin translation (thanks to s8321414).</li>
          <li>Added offline mode.</li>
          <li>The system's Dosbox and Scummvm installations are now preferred over the ones bundled with games.</li>
          <li>Improved game detection to check in all directories in the installation path.</li>
          <li>Added the option to keep game installers (thanks to Odelpasso).</li>
          <li>Added the option to disable staying logged in (thanks to Odelpasso).</li>
          <li>The preferences menu now uses a file picker for setting the installation path (thanks to Odelpasso).</li>
          <li>Startup time has been reduced.</li>
          <li>Games which aren't installed are now grayed out.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release><release version="0.9.1" date="2019-12-27">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fixed crashes and freezes sometimes happening while downloading and installing games.</li>
          <li>Fixed installation failing when the installation directory is not on same filesystem as /home.</li>
          <li>Fixed downloads crashing when the installation directory is changed or the refresh button is pressed.</li>
          <li>Fixed changing installation directory not loading which games are installed in the new directory.</li>
          <li>Fixed copyright file in deb package not being machine readable.</li>
          <li>Moved binary to /usr/games in the deb package.</li>
          <li>Add command line options --help, --version and --reset. The reset option will reset the cache and configuration.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release><release version="0.9.0" date="2019-12-25">
      <description>
        <p>Initial release.</p>
      </description>
    </release></releases>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">moderate</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-narcotics">moderate</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-tobacco">moderate</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-discrimination">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-humor">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-profanity">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-gambling">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-adultery">moderate</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-appearance">moderate</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-homosexuality">moderate</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-nudity">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-prostitution">moderate</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-themes">moderate</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">moderate</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">moderate</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-location">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-desecration">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-slavery">intense</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-worship">intense</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
</component>
